Good Morning
Good morning.
Yoo-hoo.
Today, I'll be wearing this bear hair.
Look.
Isn't he cute?
It's knit in the back.
It's Christmas today.
Oh, my gosh. It's got ears.
They have ears.
Every year, a friend of my grandmother's used to give me a Christmas cake and these boots.
Now that I've grown up, I don't get them anymore, but I'm going to pay my respects to them.
They are so cute.
And then there is Christmas.
Listen to me, everyone.
All the members are martial artists.
You know, without the bangs, oh my, oh my, oh my, oh my, shoulders.
Yes. Pavlin said he has a solo dressing room.
Oh, no. It's like I've become funny.
Her eyelashes look amazing, don't they?
I made them into a bunch.
It's done. Bon appétit.
If you're here.
I want it if you're here.
I don't want my hands to be on you.
If you're looking at it and you want to do a little bit of this from the sleeve
or something like that, if you feel like doing it.
If you want to come out as much as your body can handle...
I'm hungry.
I'm going in there.
I'll give him some Christmas water.
That's cute.
What's this? A towel.
A towel.
It's cute.
I used it.
I'll put it in the rehearsal.
I'll put it in at the rehearsal.
I'll put it in rehearsal
That's great!
That's great.
Is this a touchy subject?
I just touched it.
That's so cute.
Can I touch it?
Just a little bit.
Oh, my God.
It's like a tangle.
This won't hurt your tangle?
It sure doesn't hurt.
It's so cute.
It's cute.
Cute.
Cute Sweeve.
You're new again.
I'm totally fine.
Sweeve.
Yes, nice to meet you.
Let me be the first to greet you.
One, two, three, four, five, six, all the staff, and to all of you,
Love Network, we are super copy teachers.
Please give us your best regards.
Yes, thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Good luck.
YES!
Down the stairs over there.
Yes, sir.
We're on the third floor.
Yes, thank you.
Pops is a door note.
It was totally fine, wasn't it?
what is it?
It was totally slow.
Teteimo4n
4 days
Nakamiya, nothing cute.
You're so cute!
Ha-ha-ha!
You do it like this?
So cute!
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Oh, so cute, so cute.
Can you sit down?
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
That's amazing.
He's so cute.
Oh, my God.
You're holding my hand.
Thank you.
emen
일매
Rar.
We're in this together for life.
Cute, cute, cute, cute, cute, cute, cute, cute, cute, cute, cute, cute, cute, cute, cute, cute.
The song we deliver to each other is just a little bit
Come on, try to close it.
The sound from here is
When you smile at me ribution
Immediately
if i make it
un Disneyland
I'm baby
my only
romagnet
like a BM
I'm baby my only romagnet like a BM
Words, music, arrangement by Miku Hatsune
Ha!
and
dj
car
rehearsal condo shaggy
I'm gonna go change.
I'm dressed now.
Thank you for watching!
Today is Doki-Doki Christmas Party 2023 by Chotokimeki Advertising Department!
Thank you very much for coming to
Thank you very much.
Chotokimeki Marble.
This is Jelko and Angelea.
Thank you very much for coming.
I'm sorry if I'm disturbing the guests...
Oh, excuse me.
You laugh like Santa Claus.
To all the guests around...
Excuse me, sir.
Please note that it is forbidden to disturb the surrounding customers.
Hiorin is not singing, but you can hear her voice, so I hope everyone can enjoy the show as if Hiorin in the audience is having fun.
The show will start soon.
Are you ready to enjoy the last one-man live concert of this year?
KANAMI!
Jr.
Futoka!
Maruko!
Aki!
Yori!
Super-tokimeki Advertising Department, Rock Out!
Let's go for it!
Thank you very much.
Bye.
That's the one over there.
We'll go with two.
Heisei disinfection
Good night.
Good night
BGM
Everyone is close. I can only see the back of everyone's head.
I was going to post a picture of this bear hair on social media, but the staff,
I was told not to do that because it's too precious, so I took it until today.
So I'd like to upload it after the show. The photo.
Nobody is here. It's so beautiful outside with the illumination.
Go to the second floor, then to the back of the first floor, then to the stage.
If you can do that, it's already perfect!
What do you think?
I hear a buzz. I can hear the buzzing.
I'm coming!
전іч Чтобы This platform is the only O.K.!
P.O. has gone.
Coming! It's coming!
Huh?
They're coming!
He's coming!
See you later!
See you soon!
Thank you so much for making 2023!
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you very much!
Thank you for your hard work
Salad on the side
It was like Christmas Eve.
It was Christmas Eve.
16th.
KARAMI is doing great.
I was so excited when I thought of the Christmas that I had.
What a present!
I'm sure you're going to get a lot of presents.
I'll remember it.
Thank you very much.
Yes, you performed three new songs today.
That's great.
Everyone was listening to them, but did you enjoy them?
It was so exciting.
I was so happy that the audience was so excited that I didn't think it was a new song.
It was like a child was born after the song was performed. It was like having a baby.
It was so much fun, the new song.
We started with "WANTED," so I could hear everyone's "Oh! I was really excited to hear the new song.
But you know, it was kind of cool from the start.
Cool! I felt like a big shot.
I felt like a big shot.
It was fun.
FeverDid you have a good time?
Yeah, I did.
Oh, you gave me this with your ear.
I got it from my ear.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
Nice to meet you.
I'm so happy.
Santa Claus.
Yuu was so cute!
Santa Claus really came!
Santa Claus!
I could call you on the phone next to me.
I could touch you.
Santa Claus was right next to me.
You definitely don't need a phone.
I didn't have anywhere I wanted to go.
There's nothing in there.
He's not coming.
It's been a while since I saw Hiyori.
I'm happy.
Happy, happy, happy.
I'm happy, I'm happy, I'm happy.
So... we have another meeting tomorrow
I'll do my best.
Let's do our best.
Let's all have fun.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for watching.
Goodbye goodbye, thank you for yesterday.
After the rain, the cityscape turns colors
And on the canvas of my broken heart, I paint a piece of the future.
And lead us on the way...
Subtitle: Kiyo Hiyo
I can tell you now
When you're lost, just remember
So that I can smile even when it rains
Come on, let's go wherever you want
Goodbye Goodbye to Yesterday's Me
After the rain, the streets are shimmering
My heart is like a sunny day, puddle sounds
I play the rainbow piano
Goodbye goodbye to yesterday's me
After the rain, the streets are shimmering
My heart is like a sunny day, drying my tears
I'm gonna wear a rainbow dress
Larallala ...
Larallala...
Larallala, larallala, larallala, larallala...